(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(CAR ENGINE RUMBLING)
(CAR ENGINE REVVING)
(MUSIC PLAYING
DISTANTLY OVER RADIO)
Are you sure
we haven't passed the turnoff?
("FAVOURITE PEOPLE"
PLAYING OVER RADIO)
LILY: Yeah, I think so.
She said the turn should be
coming up here pretty quick.
♪ Call me a diamond
But don't tell me to shine ♪
♪ Straight lines
Oh, oh, oh! ♪
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
I... think you just passed it.
(SCOFFS) Lily, there's no way
that leads to a campground.
Please.
(SCOFFS) Okay.
You are the boss.
(CHUCKLES)
♪ All she ever talks about
Is making it last... ♪
This is so nice. (CHUCKLES)
I think I see a lake.
Oh, yeah. Look at that.
♪ Made of glass ♪
♪ Rihanna feels like she's
The only girl in the world ♪
♪ She wants you to stay ♪
♪ There's too much riding
On nothing diamonds ♪
♪ I gotta get outta here... ♪
(BRANDON LAUGHING)
LILY: Oh, my gosh!
It's beautiful.
(SONG STOPS PLAYING)
(BIRD CAWING)
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS) Let's go.
(PANTS, CHUCKLES)
BRANDON: Whoo-hoo!
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
BRANDON: Oh, it's perfect.
(WHISPERING) Wow, yeah.
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
And just like that woman said,
there's no one even here.
BRANDON: Come on.
(LILY CHUCKLES)
BRANDON:
Where do you wanna set up?
LILY: I don't actually
wanna set up yet.
BRANDON: What do you mean?
This place is fucking great.
LILY: I know...
I didn't mean
I didn't wanna stay here.
I just meant
that I don't wanna set up yet.
Hmm.
What'd you have in mind?
Hmm...
I don't know...
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(BOTH SMOOCHES)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(KISSES)
(GASPS) Oh! Oh, my god.
(CHUCKLES)
What? What is it?
I guess people are here.
BRANDON: Shit.
(SCOFFS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Hello.
What the fuck? Hold on.
(HESITATES) Why is he...
why is he coming?
Hey, uh... (CHUCKLES)
...can I help you
with something?
Brandon... Brandon.
Just... just ignore them.
It's fine, we can set up
and get back to that later.
No, this is...
this is messed up. Hey!
(SCOFFS) How about
a little privacy here, huh?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What the fuck, man?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(PANTS)
(PROWLERS GRUNT)
(GASPS, SCREAMS) No! Brandon!
No! (GROANS)
(LILY GASPING)
(SOBS) No!
Lily!
(PROWLER GRUNTS)
Brandon!
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
("ARROWS TO FLOWERS" PLAYING)
(PLAYERS SHOUTING, CLAMORING)
♪ Oh, baby, love ♪
Yes! Nice pass, Alex.
(SCATTERED CROWD APPLAUSE)
(LIVELY CHATTER)
♪ I don't want no... ♪
(SUPPORTERS EXCLAIMING,
CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
(SONG CONCLUDES)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(CROWD CHEERING, APPLAUDING)
PLAYER: That was so cool!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SCOFFS)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
(CROWD CHEERING, APPLAUDING)
Always the hero.
Glad you could make it, Danny.
You seem surprised.
No, I'm just glad
some mission didn't come up
that prevented you
from being here.
What could be more important
than taking my daughter
to visit a few colleges?
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
I really do appreciate
you agreeing to take her
on such short notice.
I'm happy to do it.
Just kinda surprised
you don't wanna take her.
I do. But...
The hospital changed my schedule
and I can't afford
to take that many days off.
And given that she and I
have been butting heads
about things lately,
I honestly thought
it'd be better if you took her.
You've been away a lot
these past couple years.
Hmm.
You don't have a lot of time
to reconnect with her
before she goes to college.
How does she feel about it?
Yeah...
(CROWD EXCLAIMING, CHEERING)
Nice shot, Alex!
(PLAYERS CHEERING)
That's why I'm glad
you reached out.
I'm just surprised
you have this much time off.
Actually... I retired.
What? (SCOFFS)
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
I thought
you were gonna do 30 years.
So did I.
Then they tried
to put me on a desk, and...
it's just not me.
That's the whole reason?
Yeah.
I mean, the ride lasted longer
than it probably should've.
I missed out on a lot.
What are you gonna do now?
Long term? I have no idea.
But right now, I'm just focused
on these college visits
and trying not to make things
worse with her.
JANINE: Hmm.
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(CAR ENGINE RUMBLING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(KEYS JANGLING)
(CAR ENGINE STOPS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey.
DANIEL: Hey.
Alex!
ALEX: Coming.
There's our soccer star.
Hey, Daniel.
Hi.
JANINE: All right, I think
I should get a picture
of you two before you go.
ALEX: I got it.
Alex, let's just get
a... a shot.
Mom.
No, come on. It'll be quick.
Just get closer.
Oh, come on, closer than that.
(CHUCKLES) Come on. Smile!
(CHUCKLES)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
Not bad. Okay. Uh...
Yeah.
Just call me every day.
Yes.
JANINE: I love you.
I love you too. Bye.
Okay. Please make sure
she calls every day.
I will pick up,
even if I'm on shift.
Of course.
She may not act like it now,
but one day...
she will appreciate this.
Better get moving.
JANINE: Yeah. Okay. Um...
Have a good time, you two.
Be safe. Danny.
Take care of her.
I will.
("TONIGHT" PLAYING)
Okay. Bye. Love you.
Bye. Love you.
So, we're doing this.
It's exciting.
Yeah. Totally.
♪ You didn't have to tell me ♪
♪ I already knew ♪
♪ That I had my life backwards ♪
♪ An illusion to choose ♪
(LAUGHS)
♪ I'm trading in my brass ring
Maybe now I'll find some luck ♪
♪ A moment on my hands
Forever prayer ♪
♪ Forever lost ♪
♪ Such a shame ♪
♪ What a thing to choose ♪
♪ I'm out on the gallows ♪
♪ But you're gonna save me ♪
(SONG CONCLUDES)
(CAR ENGINE STOPS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
OVER CELL PHONE)
Yo.
ALEX: Huh?
Wanna use the bathroom?
Oh, no. I'm good.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING
OVER EARPODS)
(KEYPAD BEEPS)
(GAS PUMP CLANKING, WHIRRING)
What are you watching
over there?
Nothing. Just stupid stuff.
Like what? Like cats
ice skating or something?
Cats ice skating?
Is that a thing?
DANIEL: On there,
everything's a thing, isn't it?
When I was overseas,
if we had Internet,
I'd spend hours
watching that junk.
Oh, you had Internet. Hmm.
Must've been some other reason
why I barely heard
from you then.
Let me guess.
Operational security.
DANIEL: Yeah, we take
that kinda thing...
Yeah.
...seriously in a combat zone.
Good. Good.
No, 'cause I was just starting
to think you didn't care, but...
Alex, come on, you know
I didn't have a choice.
Technically, it is a choice
to join the army.
So... yeah, you kinda did.
DANIEL: Alex, I was a soldier.
Yeah, I know.
DANIEL: And it's not just
what I did, it's who I was.
It's what I felt like
I was called to do.
And I am sorry that it took me
away from you and your mom.
But you loved it,
and you'd do it again, right?
Wouldn't you?
Yeah. (CHUCKLES) Okay.
You know what?
I am gonna use the bathroom.
(SCOFFS, SIGHS)
(SOLEMN MUSIC PLAYING)
You're carrying. Right?
Of course I am.
Right. Well, put it away.
What?
Lock it up.
Alex, I am a highly-trained
soldier, I was--
God forbid someone actually
sees you with that thing
and thinks I'm a redneck
or something.
You shouldn't care
about what people think.
Look, if you can't even do
this one thing for me, it's...
it's okay. Mom can pick me up.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
ALEX: It's really not that far.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(SOLEMN MUSIC BUILDS)
Close your door.
(KEYS JANGLING)
There.
We good?
Thank you, Daniel.
You know, if you're not going
to call me Dad,
you could at least...
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
DANIEL: You could at least
call me Danny.
My mom called me Daniel.
(UPBEAT MUSIC
PLAYING OVER RADIO)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
ALEX: Thank you.
DANIEL: Thanks.
It seems like
there's a dress code.
If you're too embarrassed
to be seen, you can just wait
in the truck, you know?
No, I wanna go
to the parents thing.
See what this place
is all about.
Okay.
Just so you know,
all you have to do is
bring back any forms
they give you
and say that
this is my top choice.
Is it?
I just need you to say it is.
Okay.
Thanks.
I'll see you after. Okay?
DANIEL: Copy.
(MAJESTIC CHORAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHOIR VOCALIZING)
(SIGHS)
DIRECTOR: Hello, everyone.
Thank you so much
for joining us this afternoon.
As we go around,
please let us know
what your child's
favorite subject is,
what major
they intend to pursue,
and any activities
or hobbies they're into.
Um, we'll start with you, sir.
In the flannel shirt.
Uh, yeah.
My daughter is Alex Beckett.
DIRECTOR: Mm-hmm.
She plays soccer.
Hmm.
And I think she's...
pretty good at math
and reading...
science, you know,
all the subjects, really.
Do you know if she has
a particular major in mind?
Uh...
She's into a lot of things.
(CHUCKLES)
But I do know
that this university
is her first choice.
I see, um, just to be clear,
this is a college,
not a university.
There's a difference.
And what about you, ma'am?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
So, how'd it go?
ALEX: It was fine.
Can we go?
Sure.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey.
So, what is your favorite
class at school?
Why?
Turns out, I'm expected to know
something about your academics.
And what you wanna study.
Well, I can just
forward you my transcript.
Or we could have a conversation.
(CELLPHONE BLIPS)
Just sent it to you.
(CELLPHONE BUZZING, CHIMING)
Can't wait to check 'em out.
DANIEL: Really?
Well, then I will be
on my best behavior.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
DANIEL: Yeah.
Yeah, she's right here.
Wanna talk to your mom?
Hey, Mom. It's going great.
Love you. Bye.
Uh-huh, yeah.
Okay. We will call you
after the visit tomorrow.
Bye.
(CELLPHONE BEEPS)
What'd she want?
She wanted to let me know
that the school
we're visiting tomorrow
has a scholarship
offer on the table.
And to make sure you connect
with the soccer coach.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Nothing. No.
It's just weird
that she thinks I'd forget
to connect
with the soccer coach.
I don't know, seems like a...
normal motherly reminder to me.
ALEX: No, it is, it is.
It's just, all she's been
wanting to talk about lately
is soccer.
Don't you like soccer?
ALEX: Yeah, sure.
I mean, I'm happy
about the scholarship offers
we're getting.
Like, I know
it'll help financially, but...
Honestly, I don't even know
if I like playing soccer
that much.
And then playing it in college
is gonna take up
so much of my time, and...
there's other things I...
I don't know, I'm...
I'm into a lot more.
Really?
Like what?
Art?
What makes you say that?
Well, I did look
at your transcripts,
and I saw that you took
an art elective every semester.
It's way more
than what's required, so...
must mean you really like it.
Yeah, I do.
You wanna tell me more about it?
No, not really.
I don't necessarily
feel like faking
a deep conversation
with you right now.
DANIEL: Alex,
it doesn't have to be
faking a conversation.
If art's what you're into,
I wanna hear all about it.
No, honestly,
I'm just really exhausted.
I should probably
get some sleep, and...
it's a long day tomorrow,
you know?
(SOLEMN MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR LOCK CLICKS)
Good night.
ALEX: Good night.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(RESIDENTS CLAMORING)
MIDWIFE 1: One more push!
One more push!
Go. Go. Yes! Push!
MIDWIFE 2: Breathe. Big push.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
MIDWIFE 2:
Big push, you can do this.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
MOTHER: (SOBBING)
My baby! My baby!
ABIGAIL: That's the fifth one.
Something wrong with the girls.
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
ALEX: Bye.
Bye, Alex.
(DISTANT CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
DANIEL: How'd it go?
It was fine. I don't know.
Place seems like
a really big party school.
DANIEL: Yeah, I did see
they have a thing here
called the freshman
underwear run.
(LAUGHS) Yeah, I don't know.
I'm not really into it.
Well, we got two more
to see, right?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
I just-- I don't know
if I really wanna see
the other two schools.
Okay.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
So, I emailed this school
that I'm interested in
last night,
and they got back to me,
and they said they can
fit me in for a tour tomorrow.
Can you take me?
What school is it?
It's an arts school.
ALEX: I really wanna try to see
if there's, like,
a future in it for me and...
You know?
But if... if you're not into it,
then obviously, you know...
DANIEL: Well, I'm into it.
It's, like, a nine-hour drive
the other way though.
I'm retired.
Got nothing but time.
Wait. No.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
(LAUGHS) Okay. Okay.
Um...
(TENDER MUSIC PLAYING)
There's just
one other thing. Um...
Can you not tell Mom about it?
(SIGHS)
ALEX: I swear I'll tell her
once we get home and... and--
Alex, that's--
I'll say I made you do it.
You know, it's my fault.
Look, she just has this idea
of... of my future in her head,
and that's not me.
(INHALES, SIGHS)
Where are we headed?
(CHUCKLES)
("BLOOM" PLAYING)
Okay. Thanks.
No... no vacancy
at that one either.
Well, I'm sure
we'll find something.
Just might be a little farther
from the college.
ALEX: That's fine.
♪ Doing everything I can... ♪
You know, if worse
comes to worse...
I do have a tent in the back.
Why?
I got a lotta stuff back there.
I'm just saying, if we had to...
we could do
one night of camping.
Camping?
Yeah, like we used to.
(HESITATES) Okay, I'm going
to keep looking for a hotel.
(CELLPHONE KEYPAD TAPPING)
♪ Feel the sun
On your face ♪
♪ Full of color ♪
♪ I'm in bloom... ♪
(SONG CONCLUDES)
(GROANS) God.
Okay, I just lost my last bar
so that's that.
(SCOFFS) Oh, come on.
(SIGHS)
No service
isn't the end of the world.
Maybe we could even
have a conversation.
(SIGHS) Okay.
What do you want
to talk about? (EXHALES)
Let's talk about...
why looking at an Art college
has to be a secret
from your mom.
Because according to her,
there's no future or money
in drawing or painting.
She just wants you to be happy.
Maybe...
try being honest with her.
Like you're being honest
about your retirement?
What do you mean?
All you ever talked about
was how much you loved the army,
and how you'd wear the uniform
until they ripped it
off your back,
and now you just expect me
to believe
that you decided to retire?
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Okay. Good talk.
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(CAR ENGINE STALLS)
I'm gonna go use the bathroom.
(DOG BARKING IN THE DISTANCE)
(CAR DOOR CLOSING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(GAS PUMP CLANKING)
("YOU TOOK MY HEART"
PLAYING FAINTLY OVER SPEAKERS)
(REFRIGERATOR WHIRRING)
(CLOCK TICKING)
♪ You took my heart
And bailed away ♪
♪ You wanted me
To take your hand ♪
♪ I knew that you could
Not be changed... ♪
ABIGAIL: You like the art?
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Yeah. It's cool.
You wanna buy one?
Uh, no. No, thank you.
Do you have a bathroom?
Yeah. Through that side door.
It's real easy to find.
Thank you.
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(CROWS CAWING)
("YOU TOOK MY HEART"
CONTINUES OVER SPEAKERS)
(BOTTLES CLINKING)
(MENACING MUSIC PLAYING)
RESIDENT: Hey. Hey!
(ALEX GRUNTS)
What are you, 16?
Seventeen?
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
ABIGAIL: Is that it,
plus the gas?
Yep.
Where you headed?
(REGISTER BEEPING)
DANIEL: Well, we're driving
up to Port Winston,
but we were hoping to find
a place to stay near here.
You know of anything?
Nah, there ain't any hotels
between here and Port Winston.
Nothing, huh?
Oh, there's a bunch
of campgrounds
between here and there.
Actually, got a real nice one.
Not too far from here.
How far are we talking?
ABIGAIL: Just a few miles
up the road.
But it's real easy to miss.
Probably best
if I draw you a map.
DANIEL: Thanks. I'm gonna grab
a couple more things.
Mm-hmm.
(WELDER CRACKLING)
("I WISH YOU WERE
WITH ME TONIGHT" PLAYING)
ABIGAIL: There's a small sign
right at the turnoff.
But you wanna go slow
or you're gonna fly right by it.
You wanna make the turn,
and then it's just one mile
from that point.
I got us directions
for a campground.
Okay.
ABIGAIL:
You're gonna love the place.
It's beautiful, and you should
have it all to yourselves.
Hot dogs, chips, water.
Mm-hmm.
Anything else?
No. I'm good. Can we go?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just wanna... I just wanna go.
Seventy-eight.
Thanks again,
and keep the change.
Oh, I appreciate that.
You enjoy the peace and quiet.
Take care of each other now.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Call Stanley.
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
("THE WEEKEND"
PLAYING OVER RADIO)
♪ Pick me up in your car
Don't care what you're drivin' ♪
♪ But it better be the loud
And fancy type... ♪
DANIEL: Feels like
we're getting close.
Says we should see a mile marker
up here on the right.
ALEX: Is that it?
DANIEL: There it is.
ALEX: There we go.
Is there gonna be a campground?
I mean, it's...
not much of a map, really.
(SONG CONCLUDES)
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
DANIEL: What do you think?
ALEX: Yeah, it actually
is kinda pretty.
DANIEL: Yeah.
ALEX: I'm just worried about
not being able to take a shower
before the tour tomorrow.
Bet the lake's not that cold.
(SCOFFS) Ha-ha.
It's an art school.
I'm sure you won't be
the only person there
who hasn't showered.
Ew. Okay? That's gross.
No, I'm actually kinda
stressing about it, though.
I hear you.
This part of the trip
was not planned,
but here we are.
Yeah.
Let's try to make
the best of it.
I mean, it's gorgeous.
Yeah. You wanna set up camp?
Yeah. Let's do it.
Okay.
(GRUNTS, PANTS)
(CHUCKLES)
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
I'm impressed you still know
how to set this up.
Of course I do.
Did it, like, 10,000 times
when I was little.
Except now
I'm a lot faster at it.
Yeah, because back then,
you insisted
on doing it yourself...
(ALEX SCOFFS)
...and you wouldn't
let me help at all.
Those first couple times,
it took me over an hour
and you were just like...
"You're doing great, sweetie."
Meanwhile,
it was completely dark outside.
I respected your determination.
ALEX: Yeah.
DANIEL: Oh, man,
except for that one time.
You remember?
It was raining so hard,
we're getting drenched,
and you still wouldn't
let me help you.
Hey, at least I can talk
about resilience
in my college
application essays now.
Yeah. That was resilient.
ALEX: Yeah.
DANIEL: Yo,
speaking of college essays...
I imagine this school's gonna
wanna see some of your art.
Yeah. Of course.
Could I see some?
I'm taking you there,
shouldn't I at least
have some basic knowledge
of your work?
In case they ask me about it?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
I guess you're right. Um...
A couple sketches
I did recently,
and don't judge them
too hard, okay?
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
So cool.
Hmm.
(SCOFFS) They're just sketches.
Yeah, but the style
and the detail
is really something.
Alex, you gotta pursue this.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
You got anything else I can see?
I can show you
a few paintings I've done.
You can just swipe through.
DANIEL: What? Wow.
These are incredible.
(CHUCKLES) I have a whole
portfolio online.
I can show you
once we get service again.
Well, I can't wait
to see it all.
(CHUCKLES)
(SHIVERS)
Cold?
Yeah.
Let's see if we can
find some dry wood.
Make a fire.
Yeah.
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(BIRDS CALLING, CHIRPING)
How much more
do you think we need?
Let's hope this stuff burns.
ALEX: Yeah, it's all pretty wet.
(BIRD SCREECHING)
What was that?
DANIEL: I don't know.
Animal, maybe?
Yeah.
(CLACKING IN THE DISTANCE)
Yeah, I heard that.
Like, back in that area, yeah?
Yeah.
Time for a little recon by fire.
(GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES)
(ROCK THUMPING)
(FOLIAGE SNAPPING)
What was that?
Gotta be, like,
a raccoon or a possum.
ALEX: Huh.
I love that one drawing
with all the faces.
Oh, yeah, I did portraits
of my friends IDs.
DANIEL: Really?
ALEX: (CHUCKLES) Yeah.
DANIEL: That's so cool.
(DISTANT WHISTLING)
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
ALEX: What is it?
It's a person.
(DISTANT WHISTLING)
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
Hey!
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Hello?
We see you.
Oh, I can see you too.
(PROWLER 1 LAUGHING)
Is that your son?
We didn't mean
to spoil your hunt.
We're gonna head back
to the campground.
We don't want any trouble.
(PROWLER 2 SNICKERING)
Move. Don't look back.
PROWLER 2: Hey! Get back here!
Run. Run!
Back to the truck.
(WALKIE TALKIE BEEPS)
PROWLER 2:
They're coming straight to you.
(TRUCK ENGINE REVVING)
They're taking the truck!
Hey!
(THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey! Hey!
(GASPS) Dad!
(SCREAMS) No, don't!
(GRUNTS)
(DANIEL GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(PANTS)
(GRUNTS)
(BONE CRUNCHING)
(SCREAMS, BREATHES HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
Back in the woods, that way!
Stop!
We don't wanna hurt the girl.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(WALKIE TALKIE BEEPS)
Jim, Cy.
We got two down, and he's headed
north towards you.
This fucker can fight.
We can hide over there. Run.
(PANTS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(EXCLAIMS, GASPS, PANTS)
DANIEL: Hey. (SHUSHES)
(ALEX GROANS, MUFFLED)
(WALKIE TALKIE BEEPING)
STANLEY: (OVER RADIO)
Jim, Cyrus, are you there?
(WALKIE TALKIE BEEPING)
STANLEY: Jim? Do you have 'em?
(ALEX WHIMPERS)
(WHISPERS) No.
(BRANCHES CRACKING)
(WALKIE TALKIE BEEPING)
STANLEY: Jim, do you copy?
CYRUS: (WHISPERS)
Tell him already.
JIM: (WHISPERS)
Shut the fuck up.
(WALKIE TALKIE BEEPING)
STANLEY:
Do you have them or not?
(WALKIE TALKIE BEEPING)
JIM: This is Jim, Stanley.
Uh, no.
(ALEX BREATHES HEAVILY)
JIM: We lost 'em.
STANLEY: What the fuck
do you mean, you lost them?
There's six of you, right?
(WALKIE TALKIE BEEPING)
JIM: Well, they ran away,
but there's nowhere
for them to go.
We'll have 'em soon, I swear.
STANLEY:
Well, you damn well better.
There's too much
at stake for us.
The next fucking thing
I better hear from you
is that you got them,
and you're on your way back.
(WALKIE TALKIE BEEPING)
JIM: We're fucked.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
Who... who are those guys?
I have no idea.
ALEX: Do you think they killed
that guy in the corner?
I don't know.
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
DANIEL: We gotta get outta here.
Yeah.
Just wait.
(FLIES BUZZING)
(WHEEZES, BREATHES HEAVILY)
Hey, hey. (SHUSHES)
Just breathe. Just breathe.
I knew... I knew something
was off with that guy
at the gas station.
I knew it, I knew it,
and I didn't tell you.
I should've said something.
Alex. (SHUSHES)
ALEX: (SOBS) Over and over again
and over and over again.
Look, don't make
any noise, honey. Don't.
Don't.
(SOBS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(GASPS) You're bleeding.
You're bleeding.
This is nothing. Look.
It's fine.
They're gonna--
I'm fine. It's nothing.
Okay?
(WHEEZES, BREATHES HEAVILY)
DANIEL: Alex.
Alex, focus. Look at me.
Look at me.
I know you're scared.
I know you're scared,
but I need you focused
if we're gonna get
through this, okay?
Okay. Okay.
DANIEL: So, you gotta trust me.
Okay.
Can you do that?
Yeah. Yeah.
DANIEL: Yeah?
(BREATHES HEAVILY, WHIMPERS)
Do you know where we are?
I'm gonna figure it out.
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHIMPERS)
Let's go this way.
(BREATHES SHAKILY, SNIFFLES)
(GROANS)
(WHISPERS) Come on. Stay low.
(SIGHS)
(GASPS, BREATHES SHAKILY)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
These tablets get the germs out.
(WATER SLOSHING)
Drink.
(GULPS)
I don't understand how
you're not more upset with me.
I made you lock the gun
in the truck.
Alex.
ALEX: I don't even know
what I was thinking.
It's my fault that we're
in this situation now, you know?
Alex, don't.
None of this is your fault.
Listen to me.
I have been
in much worse spots than this
over the years.
And I've always
made it through. Always.
And that's when I wasn't trying
to protect the person
I love most in this world.
We are going
to get through this.
I promise.
These guys don't know it yet,
but they messed
with the wrong dad.
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
ALEX: What? What is it?
DANIEL: You see that gap
between the trees?
There are
no straight lines in nature.
No, there are not.
(ANIMALS CHITTERING)
(BIRDS CALLING)
Railroad tracks
always lead somewhere.
ALEX: Which direction?
This way.
How do you know?
I don't. Just being decisive.
(DISTANT OWL HOOTING)
DANIEL: Get down.
(WHISPERS) Come here.
I think we should go
check that out.
(WHISPERS) No.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, we have to keep going.
I don't wanna go in there.
Honey, there might be something
in there we can use.
I see an antenna.
Could mean radio... weapons.
What are you gonna do,
just walk up and knock?
They're probably hiding
in there, waiting on you.
We can't go anywhere near it.
It might be empty.
(SIGHS)
Either way, we'll make sure
they don't see us coming.
How?
This way.
(VAN ENGINE RUMBLING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHES SHARPLY)
(WHISPERS) I don't hear
any movement. Okay.
Keep a hand on my backpack
and watch our six as we move in.
Okay.
DANIEL: Ready?
Yeah.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(TENSE MUSIC BUILDS)
(GROWLS, BARKS)
(BOTH GASP)
ALEX: Dad!
(CYRUS SCREAMS, GROANS)
Alex, run!
(ALEX PANTS, GRUNTS)
(DANIEL GRUNTS)
(CYRUS GROANS)
JIM: Come here, you little shit!
Where do you think you're going?
(GRUNTS, PANTS)
(DANIEL PANTS)
ALEX: No!
Alex, run! (GRUNTS)
(SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY, GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS) Let me go!
(GROANS)
(PROWLERS GRUNT)
ANGUS: Come here!
(GROANS)
(ALEX SCREAMS)
Damn it, just frickin'...
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
Stop squirming! God!
(NICKY GROANS)
(CHOKES) Stop fucking moving!
(GRUNTS)
ALEX: (GRUNTS) Dad!
(DANIEL GRUNTS)
(ANGUS GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS, GRUNTS)
(ALEX GRUNTS)
(GASPS, CHOKES)
GAR: No! (SCREAMS)
(DANIEL GROANS)
No!
(GRUNTS)
(GAR GRUNTS)
(GROANS, PANTS)
(GRUNTS)
I'm gonna rip
your fucking heart out! (GRUNTS)
(PANTS) Dad! No!
(GAR GRUNTS)
(ALEX GRUNTS)
(DANIEL GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
ALEX: Dad! No!
(DOG BARKING)
ALEX: Dad!
(GRUNTS, GROANS)
Let's go!
(PANTS)
(GRUNTS)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(PANTS)
(PANTS, GRUNTS)
Alex!
(GROANS)
Alex, are you okay, honey?
My ankle. (WHIMPERS)
We... we killed
that guy, and I...
and I helped you and his knife
was like, right there.
(SHUSHES)
And there was so much blood.
(SOBS) I was on his shoulder.
Alex, Alex, sweetheart.
You did what you had to do.
It's us or them. Okay?
Why are they trying to take me?
I don't know.
I don't understand.
All right, baby,
come here, come here.
I know, but I got you.
(LILY BREATHES HEAVILY)
Okay? Now,
do you think you can walk?
Huh?
I think so.
Okay, 'cause we gotta
get moving.
All right, let me help you up.
(PANTS, GROANS)
All right, let's go,
let's go, let's go.
(BREATHES HEAVILY, GROANS)
Fuck.
We need help.
We should go back and get help.
We're not going nowhere
without that girl.
Keep your shit together.
Nicky's dead, Angus.
I can fucking see that, Gar.
Do you wanna be the one
to go back to tell Stanley
that Nicky's dead?
And we didn't get the girl?
How do you think he's
going to react, huh?
JIM: Let's go, boys.
We don't got all night.
What about Nicky?
JIM: We'll come back
for him later.
Fuck.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
How's that ankle?
Yeah, it's okay.
DANIEL:
I think we should rest that leg.
ALEX: I can keep going.
DANIEL: If we don't rest,
we make ourselves
more vulnerable.
(ALEX PANTS)
DANIEL: Let's check out
this spot. It looks good.
All right, let me
take a quick look.
ALEX: Okay.
Nice.
This is perfect.
You can see or hear
anyone coming.
They won't be able to
see us once it gets dark.
Okay.
You brought all that
for college visits?
It's a habit.
Never hurts to be prepared.
Look. I got your favorite.
Maple pork sausage patty.
Mm. Yummy. (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
DANIEL:
Didn't think I'd be eating
another one of these
for a while.
What's the real reason
you left the army so suddenly?
Obviously, you loved it.
Mom and I thought you were
gonna do another ten years.
Truth is...
I got in a fistfight
with my C.O.
What happened?
My last op went kinda sideways.
We were just going back
to evacuate some local personnel
we worked with.
But people found out.
And it was chaos.
Just so many people
trying to escape.
Families. Kids.
There was one guy who
tried to hand me his baby
across the barbed wire
before we took off.
Yeah, just begging me
to take her.
And I tried to.
My C.O. got pissed.
He ordered me to leave her.
Said this is not
why we're here.
When I refused,
he got in my face.
And I lost it.
So...
My retirement wasn't
exactly voluntary.
And the baby?
She didn't make it outta there.
I'm sorry, Dad.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
ALEX: Can I ask you
one more thing?
Sure.
Did you win the fight
with your C.O.?
Oh, I whooped his ass.
(CHUCKLES)
DANIEL: Real good.
ALEX: Good.
I think I'm done. (CHUCKLES)
DANIEL: Alex.
When I was over there,
it put me
in a certain headspace.
I didn't know
how to be that guy...
and then hop on the phone
with you and be a dad.
But I should've found a way.
And I'm sorry.
Yeah. Thank you.
And I know. I know.
God, I'm tired.
DANIEL: Yeah?
Yeah. It's getting cold.
DANIEL: All right. Here.
You can use this.
ALEX: Thank you.
I'll come up there
to keep you warm.
Here. Come here.
I might just close my eyes
for a few minutes.
Yeah, go ahead.
I'll stay on watch.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
I need to go to the bathroom.
Yeah?
Yeah.
My ankle feels better.
Well, that's great.
Yeah.
I'll be right back.
Don't go far.
Yeah.
Now, you two stay close.
I'm going to go up top
and I'll meet you
by the north fork.
And for the love of God,
shut the fuck up.
I can hear you over a mile away.
Come on, come on, come on.
Follow me.
I told you to shut the fuck up!
Yeah, just keep your mouth shut.
Ah!
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(CYRUS WHISPERS) Take a break.
(SHUSHES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(YELPS)
Dad, I found her.
(BOTH GRUNT)
Fuck it. Go. Come on.
(GASPS)
She's this way!
(BOTH GRUNT)
(YELPS)
ALEX: Dad, run! They're coming!
Go! Across the river.
Oh, my god!
Go! We got him!
Let's go. Let's go. Push!
Go, go!
Don't hit the girl.
They're crossing the river,
straight at you.
DANIEL: This way.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
DANIEL: That way.
Okay. Okay.
DANIEL: Go!
You, go that way.
Oh.
We need to jump.
ALEX: No, no, no, no.
Yes. You have to trust me.
It looks deep enough.
Go. Boys, this way!
There's no other choice, Alex.
Go!
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
(COUGHING)
Alex!
Are you okay? Are you okay?
There! There!
Get under the water!
I see them! I'm gonna get 'em!
Stop! You're gonna hit her!
(GASPS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
ALEX: How far? (GASPS)
DANIEL: You're all right.
You're all right.
ALEX: Okay. (BREATHES HEAVILY)
(COUGHS)
You okay? You okay?
ALEX: Yeah, I'm good.
Oh, uh, Dad! Dad! Dad!
DANIEL: Hey!
Dad! Dad!
(YELPS) Dad! Dad! Dad!
(BOTH GRUNT)
(GASPS)
That's enough.
(GRUNTS)
No! No! No!
No! Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad!
Dad! No!
No! Dad! Dad!
(SHOUTS) Dad! Dad!
(SCREAMS, PANTS)
Might not wanna look
at this, sweet girl.
ALEX: No! Dad!
(GASPS)
Get her outta here.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
ALEX: (ECHOES) Dad! Dad!
JANINE: (ECHOES)
Danny, take care of her.
ALEX: (ECHOES) Dad! Dad!
DANIEL: (ECHOES) I will.
(GASPS)
(COUGHS)
(GROANS)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
DANIEL: ALEX
(PANTS)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(BROODING MUSIC PLAYING)
(BIRDS COOING)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(GAR GRUNTS)
(GUN CLICKS)
That's enough.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
ALEX: Hello?
Hello?
(ECHOES) Help!
Help!
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Hello!
Here, you should drink this.
ALEX: Where am I?
Please don't yell.
He really hates that.
I was brought here
just like you.
I was scared
and I tried to fight.
And it didn't work. Okay?
It just made things harder
and you don't want that.
(EXHALES) My advice...
is to just do what they say,
okay?
ALEX: No!
(DISHES CLATTER)
Please don't yell.
(DOOR SLAMS OPEN)
What's all the yelling about?
Let me go.
You're scared.
And I understand that.
I'm sorry, but that'll pass.
Lily was scared when
she first got here.
But now she's grateful
that we've welcomed her
into our family.
Isn't that right, Lily?
Yes, Stanley.
You see?
We're trying to create
something special here.
And you, of all people,
I thought would
understand that.
Fuck off.
Is this yours?
It's beautiful work. Truly.
When I flip
through these pages...
I can see you view
the world differently.
Just like I do.
(BROODING MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Tired?
MARCUS: Yeah.
Sleep would be nice.
RAY: Yeah.
Toughest one yet.
(EXHALES)
MARCUS: Yeah, fuck me.
Your pop couldn't choose
a girl with like a... IT father?
Boys. Got a beer.
Yo, can I bum one of those?
RAY: Thought you quit.
See how beautiful that is, Lily?
Beautiful.
We need more
of this beauty around here.
It's just gonna take some time.
Trust me.
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
Just give it some time.
STANLEY: (GRUNTS) Shit.
LILY: Alex. Come back!
RESIDENTS:
Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Come back!
Let her go! Let her go.
I expect you to get her in line.
Come with me.
(GROUP SHOUTING, CLAMORING)
(GRUNTS)
The fu--
Yo. Make me a couple eggs too?
Yeah, how you want 'em?
Scrambled's fine. (GROANS)
BARTENDER: 'Kay.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
God damn it. What now?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(PANTS)
No. No. No. No.
No, no.
(WHIMPERS)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
Fuck. (SOBS, BREATHES SHAKILY)
If you keep an open mind,
you'll learn to love this place.
You're strong-willed,
and I appreciate that.
But I need you
to come back with me
without making a fuss right now.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
Okay, fellas.
So, who's gonna tell me...
how I get my daughter back?
Why don't you
just fuck off, asshole?
She's gone.
Okay? She's fucking gone.
Yeah, um...
Okay, wait, wait, wait. Wait!
(SCREAMS)
Ah, my fucking fingers,
you motherfucker!
Fuck!
(GROANS) Fuck!
MARCUS: Come on.
(RAY GRUNTS, GROANS)
I'm not fucking around.
Tell me where my daughter is.
You're too late. (CHUCKLES)
She's probably gettin' it
from one of the boys
real good right now. (CHUCKLES)
And loving every inch of it.
Ah, I just...
No, no. Stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop!
Stop! Stop! (SCREAMS)
(CHOKES, GURGLES)
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
Right now, your friend here
is trying to breathe.
It's not gonna work.
With every gasp,
he's just filling his lungs up
with more and more blood.
Drowning himself.
But it's gonna take a long time.
Definitely not a fun way to go.
So, the rest of you
have a choice right now.
Starting with you.
Fuck.
Where is my daughter?
Don't say shit, Cy.
I ain't saying shit.
Don't tell him.
DANIEL: All right.
RAY: Don't.
Don't tell him shit.
Not fucking saying anything.
Where is she?
I'm not gonna ask you again.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS) She's on the island.
Cy! Cy! Shut up.
What island?
No?
(GRUNTS)
No, no, no! What are you...
what are you doing?
No! Stop! (SCREAMS)
Jesus! Fuck!
Fuck! (SCREAMS) Fuck!
(SHOUTS) What island?
The island where we live.
Stop... stop, stop, stop.
No. I'm not gonna stop.
Fuck! Oh, fuck.
Stop, please, please.
Why did you take her?
Make it stop.
Why did they take her?
Tell me or I'm gonna
slit your throat!
Stop! Don't hurt him.
I'll tell you. I'll tell you.
All right. They took her
to breed her.
All right? Stop.
What the fuck did you just say?
It doesn't matter what I said.
CYRUS: Oh, my ear.
It's like he told you.
Your girl is gone.
Leave him alone.
You got about
two more seconds to tell me
what the hell is going on.
Cy...
CYRUS: No, no, please!
Damn it, Ray!
Just call your dad.
Please!
DANIEL: His dad?
CYRUS: This is fucking crazy.
Fucking idiot!
Who's his dad?
(STUTTERS) Stanley Dixon.
He's the one
that calls the shots.
God damn it, Cy. If you say
one more fucking word...
One more fucking word,
and I will be the one to--
DANIEL: Shut up.
(GROANS)
Haven't talked to you yet.
Is he telling the truth?
Yes.
And this Stanley told you
to take my daughter?
(SCREAMS) Fuck! Yes!
We need more women 'cause ours
can't have babies anymore.
At least none that survive.
It's been going on
a few years now.
There's toxins
in the water or something.
(GROANS) Fuck!
So, how do we find this asshole?
DANIEL: (OVER RADIO)
Stanley Dixon, do you copy?
(STATIC CRACKLING OVER RADIO)
(RADIO BEEPS)
DANIEL: (OVER RADIO) Stanley.
You might want to pick up.
I have your son.
Where's my daughter?
STANLEY: (OVER RADIO)
Look who's back from the dead.
I've got your son, Ray.
And some of your other men.
Well, one less man now.
Where is my daughter?
What's your name?
You know mine,
it only seems fair.
DANIEL: Danny.
STANLEY: Well, Danny,
I can assure you,
there's no need
for any further bloodshed.
Your daughter's fine.
It was never my intention
to bring harm to her.
DANIEL: I know
what your intentions are,
you sick bastard.
I'd say they're pretty harmful.
STANLEY: That's because
you don't know me.
You don't know
what I've built here.
I wanna talk to Alex.
Right after I hear
my son's voice.
Say hi to your dad, Ray.
(GROANS) Fuck!
Go fuck yourself,
you son of a bitch!
Get the fuck off of me! (GROANS)
DANIEL: Happy?
It doesn't sound like
he's being treated very well.
Oh, he's not.
STANLEY: That's disappointing.
DANIEL: Where is my daughter?
STANLEY: She's right here.
Alex. Say hello to your daddy.
Dad! Dad!
Dad, you're alive!
Help! Dad, help!
Alex, are you all right?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
You satisfied?
If you want to see
your son alive again...
you bring my daughter here
and you come alone.
You understand?
You know, you may as well
just kill me now,
Because there is no way
you or your daughter
is ever making it
outta this alive.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC BUILDS)
(EXHALES, SNEEZES)
(STOVE WHISTLES SOFTLY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(GRUNTS)
(CAR ENGINES START)
(GROUP GROANING)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
You guys stay here.
Just me and the girl
from this point.
You got it, Stanley.
Vic. Don't fuck this up.
No, sir.
ALEX: Hey... (GRUNTS)
Let's go see your daddy.
(CAR APPROACHES)
(CAR DOOR OPENING)
(ALEX GRUNTS)
(ALEX VOCALIZES)
Not a word.
DANIEL: It's okay, honey.
This will all be over soon.
I've had the gas running
in here for the last half hour.
So, you're gonna wanna put
that gun away
before you blow us all to hell.
STANLEY: Well, look at you,
Mr. Resourceful.
But I don't give a shit.
You all right, son?
Not fucking great.
He fucking cut my finger off.
STANLEY: You see, that shit
don't sit right with me.
I took care of your daughter
like she was my own.
Look at her,
she's all in one piece.
You'd have done
the same thing if you were me.
No, I wouldn't.
You don't love your family?
Seems like we have different
definitions of love.
STANLEY: Well, maybe
that's because you've never been
put in a position where you were
about to lose everything.
Everything that you worked for,
everything that you built
and cared about over the years.
Slowly being stripped
away from you.
We didn't start this.
STANLEY: The fuck you didn't!
You're just like
the rest of 'em.
We live in a peaceful paradise.
Completely self-sufficient.
Away from society's bullshit.
And then they come over here
with their chemical plants,
poisoning our waters
and ruining our fucking lives.
And you think they give a shit?
Do you give a shit?
No.
So, desperate times
call for desperate measures.
DANIEL: Then how about we get
this over with?
And you and your son can go back
to your little paradise.
Please.
Leave my daughter and me alone.
How's that sound?
Send him over.
(STATIC SOUNDS)
Dad, they have a bunch of guys
waiting outside, we need to go.
DANIEL: What?
I'll get you, motherfucker.
(GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Fuck!
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
Dad! Dad!
Get him!
Get inside!
Alex, get down!
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(EXPLOSION)
(GASPS)
(LOUD RUMBLING)
What happened? What was that?
I think we're safe now.
Really?
Yes, baby.
I think it's all over.
Okay. Okay.
(SMOOCHES)
Oh, my God. (SOBS)
I missed you.
I missed you too.
I'm so glad you're back.
I'm so glad you're safe.
It's gonna be okay.
All right. Let's get outta here.
You okay?
Just don't look.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(STANLEY GROANS SOFTLY)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
DANIEL: You nervous?
Yeah. Kinda.
Place is a lot bigger in person.
You are gonna do great here.
DANIEL: And it's not too late
to take that gap year.
ALEX: Uh-huh, Dad.
JANINE: Your dad and I
could not be more proud of you.
DANIEL: But if it sucks,
we're only an hour flight away.
ALEX: Dad!
DANIEL: I'm just saying.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
ALEX: Whoa, that's really good.
I think that's me.
Alex!
Carrie.
It's so great
to meet you in person.
So nice to meet you too.
These are my parents.
Hi.
JANINE: Hi.
I'm Janine, this is Danny.
Hi, Carrie.
CARRIE: Hi.
We've heard a lot
about you from Alex.
You as well. (CHUCKLES)
Um, listen,
you can toss your stuff.
You can unpack later.
Um, the RE's having a meetup
in about five minutes
over in 111.
You'll be able to meet
everybody else on this floor.
Cool. Uh, sounds good.
Well, just give us a second?
Yeah, whenever you're ready.
Sweet. Thanks.
So, I guess this is bye for now.
Okay.
ALEX: Mom,
it's not like I'm going
to study abroad or anything.
(CHUCKLES)
I'll just be here, and you can
visit any time, and...
I'll be home for Christmas
and Thanksgiving.
I know.
ALEX: Right.
Oh, please don't cry.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, know that we love you.
We're thrilled for you.
I love you guys too.
And if you need anything...
I know. Really.
Gosh, it's still kinda weird
to see you guys back together.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, but it's good too, right?
No, definitely. (LAUGHS)
(UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING)
All right.
We're gonna get going.
ALEX: Okay.
But again, if you need anything.
Anything.
Call.
ALEX: I will.
Okay.
ALEX: I promise.
I love you guys.
JANINE: Love you too.
DANIEL: Love you too.
ALEX: Have a safe trip back.
Okay.
Be good.
ALEX: I will.
And if you can't be good,
be careful.
(LAUGHS) Okay.
I love you.
(EXHALES)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY, SNIFFLES)
Is everything okay?
(SIGHS) I already miss her.
(LAUGHS)
I do too.
But she's where she belongs.
Yeah.
Right.
Wait, Mom! Mom! Dad!
You still have my laptop.
Oh. Yeah.
You need that.
JANINE: Here you go.
Thanks. Bye.
ALEX: I love you guys.
We love you too.
Love you too.
ALEX: Okay. Bye.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC BUILDS)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)